[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 17, "question": "Mr. Rominger, what is your reaction to the conviction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 18, "answer": "Well, obviously, I'm a little am disappointed.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Rominger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe"]}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "What was all that about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "Well, you know, you have to understand, Joe has worked tirelessly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Is your intention not to appeal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "We will appeal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry"], "PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "Why was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Jerry did want to testify but we never made a commitment in the sense we were 100 percent positive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry Sandusky"]}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "What is your feeling about Sandusky?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "My personal feeling about Jerry Sandusky is that this is the first time that he has ever been held accountable for what he has done.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sandusky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Will they be pursuing civil action, either of your clients?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "No, at this point, the facts are still developing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "What is your sense of what should happen next?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "I'll tell you what should happen next.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sara Ganim"], "LOCATION": ["Harrisburg"]}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "WP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Are they so blinded by the aura of bib sports in this country that they did not do anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "Let me go to Sara Ganim, who is the Harrisburg \"Patriot News\" reporter who broke the story.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "What do you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Well, it's not about what I think, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry Sandusky"]}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Well, I know that Jerry Sandusky's attorney got up on the podium behind and said that he is still innocent, that he intends to fight this on appeal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "What's your reaction to the culmination of this trial?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "Well, I tend to think in terms of how victims and people who have been through this experience, how they're going to respond to it because I deal with that so much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "Is Sandusky a classic pedophile predator?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "He is, you know, in the extent that -- it depends on how you interpret what he is saying.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sandusky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "What is your feeling seeing somebody like Sandusky be convicted, be brought to book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "You feel vindicated.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sandusky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "Having been through it, what kind of courage did it take for these victims to get on the stand, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "It is the most unbelievable amount of courage you could ever imagine, you see what I go through right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "And, Michael, what are your feelings toward a man like Sandusky?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Evil, just pure, pure evil.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"], "LOCATION": ["Sandusky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Is he a classic sexual predator?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "But what do you say to them to get over the experience they have had at the hands of this monster?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Truly is an experience that you can't necessarily get over, even reliving and the courage that they had to testify is retraumatization.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "What do we do about that, do you think, looking forward, what do we do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBG", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Well, I think this is an enormous opportunity for everyone has anything to do with children, whether its schools, whether its camps, any program that deals with children, to start educating the staff, the children, the parents.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Dr. Janet, very quickly, about a Dottie Sandusky, who did take the stand, unlike Jerry Sandusky, and defended her husband, sort of practicing the \"see no, hear no, speak no evil\" philosophy of defense, I did not see anything, I didn't hear anything, do you think that she lied or is she just in some denial about all of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "``", "VBP", "DT", ",", "JJ", "DT", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "''", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "Well, it is hard to say that she lied.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Janet", "Dottie Sandusky", "Jerry Sandusky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "But what are you trying to achieve with the cable news genre, if anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "I'm only trying to achieve one thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "When you said it, did you believe it yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "It was interesting to do the speech, to work on the speech.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "If you were running a news network, what would you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Well, first of all, let me just back up a little bit and say, I don't have to live in the real world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "I mean, just talking up from your character's speech at the start of the first episode, are Americans still the hardest-working people on earth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "NNPS", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "Well, I have no idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "You didn't write that speech?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "No, I didn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Am I being too cynical here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "No, no, of course you're not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "But why do you like that solitude?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Well, I liked it then because of the drug use.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "And did you, like the Beatles, do your best stuff on the drugs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "You know what, I don't -- the last thing I want to do is make drugs sound good to anybody.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP"], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Have you arrived at a good place in your life now do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "Yes, I..", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "The hard way maybe, but you have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "I'm the luckiest guy in the world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "And without wishing to be too intrusive here, according to the photographs I saw after the premiere, you are dating a beautiful woman from \"Sex in the City,\" is this true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "RB", ",", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "''", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Every so often -- I am a single man.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["City"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["10:00 p.m."]}, "docId": "120622pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "That's \"The Newsroom,\" Sunday, on HBO, time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "``", "DT", "NNP", ",", "''", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "10:00 p.m.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"], "ORGANIZATION": ["HBO"]}}]